<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Family on Ben R Woodard</title>
    <link>/categories/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Family on Ben R Woodard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021, Ben R Woodard; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 11:42:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>
				Nehemiah 3.2 - Men Of Jericho...What?!		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/nehemiah-3-2-men-of-jericho-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 11:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/nehemiah-3-2-men-of-jericho-what/</guid>
      <description>I was looking over the biblical example of project management according to Nehemiah. If you haven&#39;t heard of this story in the Old Testament of the Bible then you are truly missing out. It is a story that begs the question &amp;quot;What can I do? I&#39;m only a(n) __________.&amp;quot; You fill in the blank. This guy was a trusted servant of the king but he was in charge of one thing, the drinks of the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Two Fish And Four Men		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/two-fish-and-four-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 12:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/two-fish-and-four-men/</guid>
      <description> ![Me and my three oldest sons with our two big fish we caught at Papa&#39;s lake cabin.](http://benrwoodard.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/photo-2-e1349698092473-768x1024.jpg)	 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Doctor Visit With 6		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/doctor-visit-with-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 18:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/doctor-visit-with-6/</guid>
      <description>[![20120730-144833.jpg](http://benrwoodard.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/20120730-144833.jpg)](http://benrwoodard.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/20120730-144833.jpg)  Ever been in one appointment rooms with 4 boys and 2 adults all at once? I hadn&amp;rsquo;t either until today. The Dr was great and the 1.5 hours passed really fast. Thankfully it was just for well child checks but with 4 crazy boys in my house I am expecting to see a lot of our pediatrician in the coming years. Hopefully they won&amp;rsquo;t always end in shots and a sad 3 year old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Baby Caden Is In The House!!!		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/baby-caden-is-in-the-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 12:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/baby-caden-is-in-the-house/</guid>
      <description>![caden-day-1](http://benrwoodard.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/caden-day-1.jpeg)  Everyday we are reminded of the tragedy and destruction that living in this fallen world brings. Hopelessness. Finality. Failure. All of these are characteristics of this world we live in.
Every once in a while though, God gives us a gift of hope and future. We see the world in a different lens when we concentrate on these gifts. It becomes a world of possibilities, bright future, and love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Spending Time With My Boys.		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/spending-time-with-my-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 14:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/spending-time-with-my-boys/</guid>
      <description>As much as I complain about having to work from home and get &amp;quot;distracted&amp;quot; all day long. I love hanging out with my boys. They are awesome. The other day I made them promise they would still hang out with me when they are teenagers.  I know it was a futile effort on my part, but I have to try. It&amp;rsquo;s not like I&amp;rsquo;m always gonna be smart and strong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Imagination Is Necessary To See God		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/imagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 20:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/imagination/</guid>
      <description>We have a [weekly parenting class](http://parentsare.us) at our church here in Summerville, SC. Currently, we are learning about AWANA and adopting the same principles that it uses to reach children to our own homes. This week we covered game time.  I know, I know&amp;hellip;&amp;ldquo;So what!&amp;rdquo;
Here is the part that got me. The games that we play with our kids are fun but the really good games all tend to have one thing in common.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				It Was Time To Sign On The Dotted Line		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/it-was-time-to-sign-on-the-dotted-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 05:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/it-was-time-to-sign-on-the-dotted-line/</guid>
      <description>Today I finalized my paperwork for the State of South Carolina and officially became the &amp;quot;managing member&amp;quot; of Wingspan Marketing LLC located in Summerville, SC. WOOHOO!!!  It has been a crazy road so far to get to this point but I believe I&amp;rsquo;m ready to take this new challenge in my life. I have to say that credit is not do to me or anyone else but my Savior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Stuck In ATL On 285/20		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/waiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 14:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/waiting/</guid>
      <description>Waiting.  Your browser does not support the video tag</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				To Hit The Mark You Have To Miss It		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/to-hit-the-mark-you-have-to-miss-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 18:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/to-hit-the-mark-you-have-to-miss-it/</guid>
      <description>I was outside with son#2 when I set up challenge for myself. I told Matthew I was going to pitch a golf ball into the cup holder of a lawn chair from about 10 feet.
Impossible? Nope, the hole is bigger than the golf ball and I have had similar luck from 137 yards. I knew all it would take is some trial and error and plenty of chances. I began to think of the similarities between setting little challenges and setting life goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Sleeping Like A Baby		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/sleeping-like-a-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 18:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/sleeping-like-a-baby/</guid>
      <description>This is what it means to sleep like a baby.  Your browser does not support the video tag</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				This Should Be On The Wall Of Every Coffee Shop (Infograph)		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/this-should-be-on-the-wall-of-every-coffee-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 11:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/this-should-be-on-the-wall-of-every-coffee-shop/</guid>
      <description>[![20110329-123611.jpg](http://benrwoodard.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/20110329-123611.jpg)](http://benrwoodard.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/20110329-123611.jpg)  See what I mean?
[Info Graph]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				A Look Back At A Great Blog, &#39;More Than Useless&#39;		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/a-look-back-at-a-great-blog-more-than-useless/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 12:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/a-look-back-at-a-great-blog-more-than-useless/</guid>
      <description>When I first began blogging I had a few blogs that inspired me every day and taught me how to create a community around my blog. &amp;quot;More Than Useless&amp;quot; was one of the first blogs I [![](http://benrwoodard.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/tomsface.jpg)](http://benrwoodard.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/tomsface.jpg)remember getting involved with. A few of my readers will remember this blog by Tom McFarlin ([@moretom](http://twitter.com/moretom)).  Tom produced some incredible articles that drew some great people into inspiring conversations. He now writes for ChurchCode and does a great job!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				What Are You Waiting For?		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/what-are-you-waiting-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 10:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/what-are-you-waiting-for/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember being at recess and having one of the boys next to you say &amp;quot;What are you waiting for?&amp;quot; This was usually the extra nudge someone (maybe you) needed to do something stupid or awesome.  How about this: &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s the worst that can happen?&amp;rdquo; There&amp;rsquo;s a phrase that has gotten many a kid in trouble at school.
Both of these phrases and so many more like them are used everyday by people trying to persuade someone else to do something that they themselves won&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Monster Jam 2011 Pensacola		</title>
      <link>/post/monster-jam-2011-pensacola-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 12:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/monster-jam-2011-pensacola-2/</guid>
      <description>Last night was Monster Jam in Pensacola, Florida. It turned out to be one of the best events I&#39;ve ever taken my sons to. Every year I want to take my sons to Monster Jam but there are several things that held me back. Each one of those reservations ended up being false assumptions.  So what were my reservations? Thanks for asking! I&amp;rsquo;d love to share because I want everyone to experience what my two oldest boys and I experienced at the Monster Jam Pensacola event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Life Just Kicked Me Between The Eyes		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/life-just-kicked-me-between-the-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 10:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/life-just-kicked-me-between-the-eyes/</guid>
      <description>I cannot believe it has been so long since my last post. Last thing I remember I was planning to go on vacation with my family to Charleston. I figured it would allow me an opportunity to gain some ground on my article writing.  Instead of me gaining ground I have slipped back to square one, almost. What&amp;rsquo;s up with that? It feels like life has done a roundhouse kick to my forehead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				What Is Valentine&#39;s Day?		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/what-is-valentines-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 14:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/what-is-valentines-day/</guid>
      <description>[Disclaimer: I love my wife. I think @supernightnurse is the smartest, most beautiful woman God ever created. I am blessed to even know her, let alone live in the same house with her. It is a miracle that we are friends. A true beauty and the beast story.]  I never really thought much about Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day before I met my wife. I can remember very little about this &amp;ldquo;special&amp;rdquo; day from my childhood as far as celebrations go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Don&#39;t Sign Your Name! It&#39;s Not Over Yet		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/dont-sign-your-name-its-not-over-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 14:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/dont-sign-your-name-its-not-over-yet/</guid>
      <description>By placing my name on a paper that I turned into my teacher at school I was saying that my paper was done. When I sign my name on a job application I&#39;m able to write with confidence that all the information that I put on the paper was accurate and complete.  Both of these events require you to do your best and then turn it in with a signature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				4 Steps To Setting Up Your Own SFPM – Single Focus Project Management		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/4-steps-to-setting-up-sfpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 22:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/4-steps-to-setting-up-sfpm/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that Single Focus Project Management or SFPM was taught by Christ. (I&#39;m not saying He is necessarily endorsing my blog article but...)  Remember when He said that the whole Law hinged on one law?
Matthew 22:37 &amp;ldquo;Love The Lord your God with all your heart and will all you soul and with all your mind.&amp;quot;
I have to say that is a great example of what I&amp;rsquo;m trying to implement in my life, but on a very practical level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Tooth Fairy: Give A Dollar Save A Dollar		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/tooth-fairy-give-a-dollar-save-a-dollar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 12:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/tooth-fairy-give-a-dollar-save-a-dollar/</guid>
      <description>The featured image is my wife @supernightnurse tying a string around Ryan&#39;s (6) loose tooth. He has an adult tooth growing right behind it and have been told, by a reliable source, that it will not come in right if this baby tooth doesn&#39;t fall out soon. If it doesn&#39;t come in right the we will have to take him to the Dentist. Do you know how much dental work is?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Job Hunting? &#34;Leave Room For God&#34; - Chambers		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/job-hunting-leave-room-for-god-chambers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 12:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/job-hunting-leave-room-for-god-chambers/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m in the process of looking for a position doing internet marketing or web development. It becomes very frustrating sometimes when I have no control over any company&#39;s vetting process.  I know that many times it has absolutely nothing to do with who I am or what I&amp;rsquo;ve submitted that the company doesn&amp;rsquo;t choose me, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop me from blaming myself sometimes.
If a company decides to go another way it must have been something I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				The Kitchen Sink Rules My House		</title>
      <link>/post/the-kitchen-sink-rules-my-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 18:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-kitchen-sink-rules-my-house/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post of a series on what I&#39;m calling **&amp;quot;Single Focus Project Management&amp;quot;**  Even if you never clean a kitchen sink in your life your going to be able to relate to this principle of life. I&amp;rsquo;m going on two weeks of keeping my kitchen sink spotless. Not just well managed but completely free of dishes and junk that seems to accumulate very quickly on an hourly basis in our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				When Showing Up Is A Victory		</title>
      <link>/post/when-showing-up-is-a-victory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 12:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/when-showing-up-is-a-victory/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes the hardest part of accomplishing a goal is simply not quitting. Life gets overwhelming very quickly. One story in scripture that has meant the most to me in times of major events is found in 1 Kings 18. Elijah, a prophet of God, is brought to his knees in self pity and feelings of being overwhelmed. At one point he asks for God to take his life.  By nature we humans can become overwhelmed in a situation and begin to withdraw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Our Holidays Went Something Like This...		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/our-holidays-went-something-like-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 20:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/our-holidays-went-something-like-this/</guid>
      <description>...minus the party.  We were privileged to have both our sets of parents down this past holiday season. One came in during Thanksgiving and and one during Christmas. It was great to share our boys with them but I know they felt like they were in the middle of a hurricane when all three were at the top of their game.
It was also the first time that I was home and totally focused (I had no where to go) on the boys for two weeks without school to break things up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				My Dad&#39;s Childhood: A Godly Heritage		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/my-dads-childhood-a-godly-heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 12:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/my-dads-childhood-a-godly-heritage/</guid>
      <description>I received an envelope in the mail a few days before Christmas last year. It was from my dad. I forgot that the last time he visited, during Thanksgiving, he mentioned he was working on a special present for me and my three siblings. He was writing about his childhood so that we would know some things about where he was from, what it was like, and how he became who he was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Phrases That Change The World		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/phrases-that-change-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 17:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/phrases-that-change-the-world/</guid>
      <description>There are certain times in life where something so simple is just overlooked by the wisest and smartest of us all. Following an extremely simple command can make a world of difference in life. Here is a short list of phrases I have learned can make or break a situation.    Keep your head down (golf)
  Keep your eye on the ball (baseball)
  Two objects cannot occupy the same space at the same time (driving)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Giving Value to the Valuable		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/giving-value-to-the-valuable/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 12:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/giving-value-to-the-valuable/</guid>
      <description>When I think of all my great memories of Christmas in the past I see that my value system is greatly influenced by what happened during these short two weeks. It is kind of scary to think that my valuable memories usually begin about 5 years old. My 6-year-old is entering a stage in life that will establish what he deems as worthy of his time and effort, not just during the Christmas but for the entire year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Narnia: The Voyage of the Dawn Treader		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/narnia-the-voyage-of-the-dawn-treader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 11:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/narnia-the-voyage-of-the-dawn-treader/</guid>
      <description>Debbie and I actually got to go out on a date and we didn’t waste the evening. We went to see Narnia: the Voyage of the Dawn Treader. The story line involves the two younger siblings and their annoying cousin. It begins and ends on the seas of Narnia. Lucy and Edmund find themselves in the water being picked up by King Caspian and the crew of the Dawn Treader who are actively seeking to find out what happened to 7 lords of Narnia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Lying To My Son Is Fun!		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/lying-to-my-son-is-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 02:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/lying-to-my-son-is-fun/</guid>
      <description>OK, it may sound horrible but it&#39;s true.  But wait! Before you start condemning me for being a child hater and a deceiver, the son of the Father of Lies, I would like to try and explain myself.
I guess I really don&amp;rsquo;t need to explain much because almost every parent in the world tells their kids something that isn&amp;rsquo;t true in order to see the child&amp;rsquo;s reaction. Right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Hoping For Big Things		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/hoping-for-big-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 18:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/hoping-for-big-things/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been busy over the last few weeks (to say the least) on a few projects that will hopefully turn into BIGGER things. First of all it has been incredible staying home with my boys, they are fast becoming my biggest support group on the planet. Recently though I asked them if they liked me staying home. My 6 year old came over to me and gave me a hug while telling me that he missed mommy being home more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Dream BIG With A Child-Like faith		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/dream-big-with-child-like-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 09:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/dream-big-with-child-like-faith/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been able to spend a lot of time around my boys over the past few weeks. One of the things that impresses me the most is the desire to do great BIG things that are absolutely impossible for them to do at their young ages. My youngest is 14 months old and he is already refusing to remain the “baby”. When he sees a crowd of crazed boys outside after church he wants down so that he can join in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Encouraging Disappointment		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/encouraging-disappointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/encouraging-disappointment/</guid>
      <description>The other weekend I made it up to Atlanta with the hopes of not only spending time with family but finally getting together with a couple of the people on twitter that have made a huge impact on my professional and personal life. It was amazing that they were even contemplating about meeting with me early Sunday morning but even more impressive was the reason that we couldn’t end up meeting up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				A Good Job		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/a-good-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/a-good-job/</guid>
      <description>I was washing windows the other morning and thought of how I would know if I was actually doing a good job at it and feel rewarded in my efforts. I came to the realization that the only way to know that i was doing a good job is by people not noticing the actual in work that I did but experiencing the effects of a job well done. I am not against any leadership making a big deal of someone putting forth good hard effort on a project but if that is all we are working for then I think we miss the purpose of doing the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Log!</title>
      <link>/post/its-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/its-log/</guid>
      <description>I believe Netflix is allowing us parents to bridge the generational gap like no other resource outside of the church.
Here is one of my favorites as a kid and I was able to introduce it today to my kids via Netflix. High five for the interwebs!
   Do you think it is necessary for dads to try and bridge some of the generational gap with their kids?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				It&#39;s My Dad&#39;s 59th		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/its-my-dads-58th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 15:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/its-my-dads-58th/</guid>
      <description>Happy Birthday Dad!  Today my dad turns 59! My dad is the type of man that ran away from home because of the &amp;ldquo;restricting&amp;rdquo; rules of my grandparents and joined the Marines. It may sound like it was a dumb reason but, a he would tell you, it was the best decision of his life. His experience in the Marines proved to him the type of man he could become.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				It sure smells fresh in here.		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This blog is all about starting from a clean slate. I thought that by 32 I would have a pretty good idea of what I was suppose do be doing career wise but...  There are a few things that I am sure of. I have a beautiful, talented, and godly wife. My three boys keep me on my toes. And I have a God who loves me enough to start with new mercies every day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
