<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WordPress on Ben R Woodard</title>
    <link>/categories/wordpress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in WordPress on Ben R Woodard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021, Ben R Woodard; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 13:20:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/wordpress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>
				3 Years Ago Today We Said Goodbye		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/3-years-ago-today-we-said-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 13:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/3-years-ago-today-we-said-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>It was 3 years ago today that I was forced to say goodbye to a good friend. It was my first blogging community. At the helm was a kind (atleast I thought he was) and giving blogger named @tomfoolery. Then on April 1, 2010 I woke up to this horror of a blog post...  Over the past few months, I’ve had a number of awesome opportunities arise online and offline – I’m passionate about them and excited for the work I’m going to be doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				I Had To Bean A Client Yesterday		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/i-had-to-bean-a-client-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/i-had-to-bean-a-client-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday afternoon was rather frustrating. I love what I do as a freelancer but it&#39;s not an easy job and there are some days that make it that much harder. My clients are great people. Many of them are hard-working, honest and great at what they do. It&#39;s my goal to just accent that with the work that I do.  Sometimes, though, I take on a client that becomes a bigger issue than I can afford and I have to cut ties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				It Was Just A Goal, Right?		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/it-was-just-a-goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 02:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/it-was-just-a-goal/</guid>
      <description>I received some incredible news almost 3 weeks ago but I was hesitant to say anything. I could hardly believe it was true. I even reached out to one of the organizers of the event and jokingly asked if there was an error in the emails that were sent out. There wasn&#39;t any errors and now I&#39;m listed as a speaker for this years WordCamp in ATL! Woot!  I&amp;rsquo;ve been going to WordCamp Atlanta every time they have held it since 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
