<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>iPad on Ben R Woodard</title>
    <link>/categories/ipad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in iPad on Ben R Woodard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021, Ben R Woodard; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 19:50:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/ipad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>
				My First Post From My iPHone		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/my-first-post-from-my-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 19:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/my-first-post-from-my-iphone/</guid>
      <description>When the iPhones first came out I have to admit I wasn&#39;t very interested in it. I was curious about it and thought it was pretty cool but really had no use for it.  At that time I was getting emails from family and friends but never really interacted that much on the interwebs.
About 5 years ago my awesome wife bought me the new Samsung Blackjack but I ended up taking it back for a nice flip phone and save the money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				This Should Be On The Wall Of Every Coffee Shop (Infograph)		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/this-should-be-on-the-wall-of-every-coffee-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 11:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/this-should-be-on-the-wall-of-every-coffee-shop/</guid>
      <description>[![20110329-123611.jpg](http://benrwoodard.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/20110329-123611.jpg)](http://benrwoodard.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/20110329-123611.jpg)  See what I mean?
[Info Graph]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Olive Tree&#39;s New BibleReader 5.0		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/olive-trees-new-biblereader-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 11:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/olive-trees-new-biblereader-50/</guid>
      <description>Olive Tree&#39;s BibleReader 5.0 is out! When I turned on my iPad and brought up my Bible from [Olive Tree](http://www.olivetree.com/learningcenter/br5/) during Church I was surprised. It just wasn&#39;t the same. I finally upgraded all of my apps and therefore got the newly released BibleReader 5.0.  There are few Bible apps out there that can compare to the elegance and practicality of Olive Tree&amp;rsquo;s app.
[I&amp;rsquo;ve compared the best Bible apps for the iPad before so if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for some options you might want to check that out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Evernote Just Works		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/evernote-just-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 14:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/evernote-just-works/</guid>
      <description>Evernote is a personal bookmarking application. It allows you to save information from webpages, photos, receipts, or anything digital to an onine directory that you organize and manage. The desktop and mobile applications work seamlessly together with the online database. (View the intro video at the end of the article)  Evernotehas become one of the most crucial apps I am using on a daily basis. It has proven itself to be a very flexible and stable application that can mold to almost any model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Mirror Your iPad On Any Monitor: Doug And I Fought About This		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/mirror-your-ipad-on-any-monitor-doug-and-i-fought-about-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 12:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/mirror-your-ipad-on-any-monitor-doug-and-i-fought-about-this/</guid>
      <description>I know that one of the first frustrations I came across with Doug (my iPad) was the inability to mirror the screen to a monitor. As with any relationship, working through the conflict resolution process only strengthened our bond to each other.  Little did I know that this was possible all along. :(
I always knew you could connect to a monitor or projector in some of the apps but they were few and far between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				A Wireless Keyboard and My iPad: First Impressions		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/first-impressions-of-a-wireless-keyboard-and-my-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 14:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/first-impressions-of-a-wireless-keyboard-and-my-ipad/</guid>
      <description>My in-laws came down yesterday with some late Christmas presents. Among the packages was a little box that held one of the greatest accessaries known to man...THE WIRELESS KEYBOARD! (insert echo)  So it&amp;rsquo;s everything that I thought and more. I had no idea that it would be as easy as it was to sync it up with the iPad, it literraly is a two clicks on the iPad, five keys on the keyboard and DONE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Which iPad Bible App Is Best?		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/which-ipad-bible-app-is-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 15:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/which-ipad-bible-app-is-best/</guid>
      <description>Since I am the worst when it comes to having a regular time of Bible study I . I am always looking for new ways to keep me focused. That is why one of the first apps I looked for was a bible for my iPad. I found three Bible apps that have been very effective in helping me maintain an effective devotional life due to their features and options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Wooden iPad Cover By Substrata		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/wooden-ipad-cover-by-substrata/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/wooden-ipad-cover-by-substrata/</guid>
      <description>I wrote and article the other week for ChurchDrop about these wodden iPad covers. My brother in Portland recently started working part time for a small wood working company called Substrata. I was skeptical of the practicality of having a hand made wood cover for my iPad but the novelty of it intrigued me. Check these photos out and then head on over to Churchdrop for more information and leave a comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				How do I build community on Twitter?		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/how-do-i-build-community-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/how-do-i-build-community-on-twitter/</guid>
      <description>I’ve talked several people recently that have asked the same question: “How do you get followers on twitter?” I don’t have a huge following on Twitter but I’ve built a very specific community in it that has been a huge help to me over the last year. “So how did I build that community?” _thanks for asking. _
Here are three simple things to keep in mind as you begin building your community online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Church Analytics: my take		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/church-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 02:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/church-analytics/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had the opportunity to monitor the analytics for my church website for a little over two years now. Like most churches Burgess Road does not have a big budget for web development so I used Google Analytics as my main monitoring device. There are many advantages of using Google analytics but ultimately it is a program that is designed to give feedback to the business world and not the unique online property of a church or a non profit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				Doug’s got new @8bit clothes		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/dougs-got-new-8bit-clothe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 23:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/dougs-got-new-8bit-clothe/</guid>
      <description>My iPad (Doug) just got some new fancy clothes and I thought I would share.  By the way, I just learned that I can very easily take a screen-shot of my iPad by holding down the top button and then pushing the round button for a moment. The screen flashes white and it&amp;rsquo;s done. Simply go to your photos and there it is. For more detailed help check out this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				It sure smells fresh in here.		</title>
      <link>/post/archivedposts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/archivedposts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This blog is all about starting from a clean slate. I thought that by 32 I would have a pretty good idea of what I was suppose do be doing career wise but...  There are a few things that I am sure of. I have a beautiful, talented, and godly wife. My three boys keep me on my toes. And I have a God who loves me enough to start with new mercies every day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
