<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SFPM on Ben R Woodard</title>
    <link>/categories/sfpm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SFPM on Ben R Woodard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021, Ben R Woodard; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 11:40:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/sfpm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>
				Milestones Destroy My Drive		</title>
      <link>/post/milestones-destroy-my-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 11:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/milestones-destroy-my-drive/</guid>
      <description>A project is made up of several goals which can also be called milestones. Each milestone is comprised of simple tasks that need completing.  I have to admit that it is exciting to complete a milestone. It&amp;rsquo;s an event that I worked hard to accomplish and is a time to rejoice. Unfortunately something happens to my drive and passion as I celebrate those small victories. Everything in me that had caused me to pull the long hours and utilize every minute of the day seems to disappear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				4 Steps To Setting Up Your Own SFPM – Single Focus Project Management		</title>
      <link>/post/4-steps-to-setting-up-sfpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 22:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/4-steps-to-setting-up-sfpm/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that Single Focus Project Management or SFPM was taught by Christ. (I&#39;m not saying He is necessarily endorsing my blog article but...)  Remember when He said that the whole Law hinged on one law?
Matthew 22:37 &amp;ldquo;Love The Lord your God with all your heart and will all you soul and with all your mind.&amp;quot;
I have to say that is a great example of what I&amp;rsquo;m trying to implement in my life, but on a very practical level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				The Kitchen Sink Rules My House		</title>
      <link>/post/the-kitchen-sink-rules-my-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 18:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-kitchen-sink-rules-my-house/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post of a series on what I&#39;m calling **&amp;quot;Single Focus Project Management&amp;quot;**  Even if you never clean a kitchen sink in your life your going to be able to relate to this principle of life. I&amp;rsquo;m going on two weeks of keeping my kitchen sink spotless. Not just well managed but completely free of dishes and junk that seems to accumulate very quickly on an hourly basis in our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
				When Showing Up Is A Victory		</title>
      <link>/post/when-showing-up-is-a-victory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 12:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/when-showing-up-is-a-victory/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes the hardest part of accomplishing a goal is simply not quitting. Life gets overwhelming very quickly. One story in scripture that has meant the most to me in times of major events is found in 1 Kings 18. Elijah, a prophet of God, is brought to his knees in self pity and feelings of being overwhelmed. At one point he asks for God to take his life.  By nature we humans can become overwhelmed in a situation and begin to withdraw.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
